Q: What do you think of Satoru Gojo?
He's a teacher!
And without him, I would have been
executed by now, so he's also—
Technically, he's my benefactor.
Technically.
That also goes for other
people, too, not just me.
Honestly, I don't know him all that well.
But there's one thing I can say for certain.
He's an idiot.
Yeah, he's an idiot.
Salmon.
But still...
He's flippant. Egotistical.
And it goes without saying, but...
He's the strongest!
JUJUTSU KAISEN
Shibuya Incident
Episode 33
Shibuya Incident - Gate, Open
Hey there, weed.
This is the third time we've met, right?
And you still underestimate
the hell out of me.
I'll kill you first.
Come on, bring it.
What's your problem?
You're the ones who said
not to run, right?
Did he just touch—
One, two...
He's only targeting Jogo.
So his earlier declaration
was just misdirection?
He's also...
stopped using his Limitless technique!
No!
He's given up on adjusting his technique,
and started focusing on
compact attacks using
cursed energy manipulation in this
space that's filling up with humans?
However, that means there's
no need to slip into the crowd.
I can just use my technique!
Don't dismiss Domain Amplification, Hanami!
This is where you're weak, right?
I knew it.
You can't use Domain Amplification and
your Innate Technique at the same time.
I remained safe only because I used
Domain Amplification to protect myself.
He's operating at this level with only basic
cursed energy manipulation and martial arts!
Satoru Gojo,
what is there that you're not capable of?!
Tsk.
He's not a cursed spirit.
I bet he's one of the incarnated
Death Painting Wombs.
He's annoying, but he comes later.
Are you sure about this?
The more you try to neutralize my technique
with your Domain Amplification,
the stronger I have to maintain my technique.
I don't think this asparagus has the
energy left to withstand that, do you?
Wha—
Satoru Gojo!
Look over here!
Hanami...
Next.
The Prison Realm is a living barrier.
It's what Genshin was reduced to.
There's nothing that cannot be
sealed in the Prison Realm.
Then of course there are conditions
to sealing something in it, right?
One minute.
Huh?
Once the Prison Realm's gate is opened,
we'll have to keep Satoru Gojo
in its effective sealing range
of four meters for one whole minute.
Hey.
I'll burn you to death!
You didn't join forces with us just to push
that impossible task onto us, did you?
Even the lives of several
thousand ignorant humans
wouldn't be enough to warrant fighting
that thing under those conditions
for a full minute.
You're getting heated up, Jogo.
It's all right.
Even though we do need a minute—
Don't let Hanami's death be in vain.
Use the humans as cover,
and focus on hit-and-run tactics!
Choso!
If you're not going to help,
I'll kill you myself!
Yeah, yeah.
Not too close, not too far.
But that's the best they can do.
The people who can't see cursed
spirits have started avoiding me.
If their numbers keep declining
and space opens up,
then I can catch Volcano Head.
No more releasing my technique
to lure it in like before.
I've revealed my goal of beating
them to a pulp in close combat,
and it'll be an issue if it keeps
its distance and coordinates with
that Death Painting to unleash
a big attack through the crowd.
I'm sorry. I can't save everyone.
So I promise to exorcise them instead!
It's still not time?!
It has to have been over
twenty minutes by now!
Not yet.
Satoru Gojo's still completely composed.
We need him much more on edge.
Meiji Shrine (Harajuku)
Hey, are you oka—
Everyone got turned into monsters...
and got on the train...
I... I was told I wasn't needed
because the train was full!
So he was here!
Damn it!
Everyone...
...got on the train?
An eight-car train is pulling in.
Please wait behind the yellow line.
Gojo-sensei!
Please do not lean on the platform doors
or reach your hands or face past them.
Train's here!
We're saved!
It's here!
Hey!
What is this?!
Ow!
It's a train!
Move!
I'm getting in!
What are you doing?!
What do we do?!
Right?
Wait!
What the hell are they thinking?
Jogo!
Man, the air smells so nice here.
It's full of fear.
Let's leave a few humans alive after all.
We can release them into the woods
on weekends and go hunting!
Can I burn the forest down with them in it?
Hanami'll get mad over that.
Hanami is dead.
Seriously?
What...?
JUJUTSU KAISEN
I really can't hit you!
Patchface!
The one Nanami and Yuji talked about?!
Let me tell you one of the
gross things about humans.
There are too many of them!
So there are either cursed spirits
or curse users above us, too.
Blood Manipulation: Convergence.
Idle Transfiguration: Soul Multiplicity.
Supernova.
Body Repel.
Satoru Gojo isn't like Yuji Itadori.
I know he's capable of cold logic.
He probably assumes
some degree of sacrifice
is needed as he makes certain to exorcise us.
But with both the death count and
the number of living people rising,
the scales determining what degree
is acceptable can no longer function.
What you need to do right now
is use your Infinite Void to
kill us and all the people here
so you can save the people
outside of your domain.
But you're incapable of doing that.
Because the sacrifices
you're willing to accept
are "people killed by cursed spirits,"
not "people killed by Satoru Gojo."
Now, think.
Ponder it.
Focus your mind!
For real?
Domain Expansion:
Infinite Void.
It was a desperate gamble on a Domain
Expansion lasting two tenths of a second.
Two tenths of a second was the limit
Satoru Gojo set purely on instinct.
It was the amount of time he believed
non-sorcerers could
withstand being in Infinite Void
without becoming vegetables
or facing after-effects.
During that two tenths of a second,
roughly half a year's worth
of information flowed into
the brains of the non-sorcerers
and transfigured humans present,
rendering every one of them
unconscious while standing upright.
However, all the survivors from B5F
were able to return to
society two months later.
That's how limited his Infinite Void was.
Of course, that meant the special-grade
cursed spirits could reawaken at any moment.
So, with their potential
counterattack in mind,
Satoru Gojo narrowed his focus
on the transfigured humans.
After dismissing his domain,
the strongest sorcerer of the modern age
slaughtered all of the roughly 1,000
transfigured humans unleashed upon B5F
in 299 seconds.
Prison Realm, Gate Open.
It's all right.
Even though we do need a minute...
Hey,
Satoru.
Huh?
Long time no see.
A fake?
A transformation technique?
No, it's really him!
It's only a minute in Satoru Gojo's mind.
You shouldn't lose yourself in thought
in the midst of battle, Satoru.
I can't sense any cursed energy.
I can't get my body to move, either.
This is checkmate, huh?
So, who the hell are you?
I'm Suguru Geto.
Don't you remember me?
How sad.
Your body, your cursed energy...
All the information provided by these
eyes is telling me you're Suguru Geto.
But...
By soul is rejecting all that!
Now, answer me already!
Who the hell are you?!
Creepy.
How could you tell?
That's my technique, you see.
I can pass from one body to another
by replacing its brain with myself.
Of course, I'm also able to use the
technique etched into the body I inhabit.
I really wanted this man's curse
manipulation and this situation, too.
You didn't have
Shoko Ieiri handle the disposal of
Suguru Geto's body that day, did you?
That was an odd time for
you to show consideration.
But thanks to that, I was able
to obtain this body with ease.
You needn't worry.
I'll release your seal eventually.
A hundred... no, maybe
a thousand years from now?
You're just too strong.
And you're in the way of my plans.
Hah! Have you forgotten?
Who was it that beat the crap out
of that body before I killed him?
Yuta Okkotsu, huh?
I just don't see as much appeal
in that boy as you do.
Copying techniques without any conditions,
and a bottomless well of cursed energy...
Both of those were just effects obtained
from binding the soul of his
most beloved with a pact.
Sorry to say this,
but Yuta Okkotsu can never replace you.
Goodnight, Satoru Gojo.
We'll meet again in the new world.
What's the matter?
Something in my ear.
Can you hear me, Yuji Itadori?
Huh?
There's no time.
Listen and understand the first time.
Satoru Gojo has been sealed.
What do you think of skin care?
What? You're asking me that? Not that I mind.
I do all kinds of things, but like,
it ultimately comes down to genetics.
I'm sure those with pale, smooth skin
like Gojo-sensei would say,
"I don't really do anything."
Next time, "Pandemonium."
Next Episode
Pandemonium
So what do you actually do?
Nothing, really.
Grr!